Guide to the Oregon State University Military Photographs Collection 1875-1975
Oregon State University Libraries, Special Collections & Archives Research Center
- Cold War Years, 1946-1975; Series V
  - OSU ROTC Cadets visit to Ft. Lewis 1963, April 1963; Negatives packaged in rolls with envelopes
    - ROTC Visit to Ft. Lewis, 1963 - 2nd Place U of W, April 1963; P002:263; 5X7 photographic print (Box 2)
      Stock US Army Photograph of the ROTC 11th Regiment of Pershing Rifles visit to Ft. Lewis Washington, April 1963. The US Army stock photograph is annotated on the reverse in blue carbon typing by the photographer, Sp4 William L. Durfee of the 124th Signal Battalion. "Second Place Winners of the 11th Regiment of Pershing Rifles Drill competition, which was held at Fort Lewis, Washington, Drill team is, University of Washington, Seattle, Washington."
    - ROTC Visit to Ft. Lewis, 1963 - Officers, April 1963; P002:264; 2.0 print; 5X7 photographic print (Box 2)
      The US Army stock photograph is annotated on the reverse in blue carbon typing by the photographer, Sp4 William L. Durfee of the 124th Signal Battalion. "Talking about the diffen(sic) Drill Teams, are L-to-R, Maj. Horace E. Pierce, 10th Corp ROTC Affairs Officer, Col. Walther A. Guntharp, Commanding Officer, 1st Battle Group, 12th Infantry, 4th Infantry Division, Fort Lewis Washington and Col. John W. MacIndoe, Commanding Officer, 2nd Battle Group, 39th Infantry, 4th Infantry Division, Fort Lewis Washington."
    - ROTC Visit to Ft. Lewis, 1963 - 2 Officers in Dress uniforms, April 1963; P002:265; 5X7 photographic print (Box 2)
      The US Army stock photograph is annotated on the reverse in blue carbon typing by the photographer, Sp4 William L. Durfee of the 124th Signal Battalion. "(L-to-R) Maj. Horace E. Pierce, 10th Corp ROTC Affairs Officer and Col. Walter A. Guntharp, Commanding Officer, 1st Battle Group, 12th Infantry, 4th Infantry Division, Fort Lewis, Washington, talking over about the drill teams."
    - ROTC Visit to Ft. Lewis, 1963 - Mess Sgt. briefing, April 1963; P002:266; 5X7 photographic print (Box 2)
      The US Army stock photograph is annotated on the reverse in blue carbon typing by the photographer, Sp4 William L. Durfee of the 124th Signal Battalion. "Stc Calvin Havens, Mess Sgt. Hq. Co. 12th Inf 1 st Battle Group, 4th Infantry Div Fort Lewis Washington, explains to (L-to-R) Cadet Roger Stubbs, Cadet Maj. Roger Johnson, Cadet Rod commons and Cadet Col. Dell Ball the duties of a mess Sgt."
    - OSU ROTC cadets Mortar inspection, Ft Lewis visit 1963, April 1963; P002:267; 5X7 photographic print (Box 2)
      The US Army stock photograph is annotated on the reverse in blue carbon typing by the photographer, Sp4 Conrad R. Cheatham of the 124th Signal Battalion. "Sp4 George Howell, E Co., 1st Battle Group, 12th inf 4th Inf Div explains the 81 mm mortar to the cadets of Oregon State College."
    - ROTC Visit to Ft. Lewis, 1963 - Gonzaga drill team, April 1963; P002:268; 5X7 photographic print (Box 2)
      The US Army stock photograph is annotated on the reverse in blue carbon typing by the photographer, Sp4 William L. Durfee of the 124th Signal Battalion. "Gonzaga University, of Spokana(sic) Washington, taking part in the 11th Regiment of Pershing Rifles Drill Competition which was held at Fort Lewis Washington."
    - ROTC Visit to Ft. Lewis, 1963 - 3rd place winners, April 1963; P002:269; 5X7 photographic print (Box 2)
      The US Army stock photograph is annotated on the reverse in blue carbon typing by the photographer, Sp4 William L. Durfee of the 124th Signal Battalion. "Third place winners of the 11th Regiment of Pershing Rifles Drill competition, which was held at Ft. Lewis, Washington; Drill team is, University of Alaska, Fairbanks, Alaska."
    - ROTC Visit to Ft. Lewis, 1963 - Machine gun briefing OSC Cadets, April 1963; P002:270; 5X7 photographic print (Box 2)
      Collection of photographs of the ROTC 11th Regiment of Pershing Rifles visit to Ft. Lewis Washington, April 1963. The US Army stock photograph is annotated on the reverse in blue carbon typing by the photographer, Sp4 William L. Durfee of the 124th Signal Battalion. "Sfc Jerald Mc Kinley (R), explains to Cadet Col. Dell Ball, Cadet Maj. Roger Johnson, Cadet Roger Stubbs of Oregon State College the 30 cal Machine Gun."
    - Pershing Rifles sponsor, Molly Perry 1962, circa 1962; P002:331; 8X10 photographic print (Box 2)
      Standard head shot of coed sponsor for the OSC Pershing Rifles 11th regiment. Identification on reverse: "Eleventh Regiment, Miss Molly Perry, Honorary Sponsor Eleventh Regiment, Sponsored by Company E-11, Oregon State University" The "year" 62 is written in pen on reverse as well.
  - ROTC Pershing Rifles Drill Teams/Competitions 1960-1964, 1962
    Grouping of negatives and prints showing scenes of the OSU Pershing Rifles Drill team in competitions. One group of photos is identified as: Sand Point Naval Air Station, April 1962. Negatives are of various drill team formations inside the hangar. Showing the grandstands with spectators and the large doors with windows of the hangar, the negatives may have been used in OSU Barometer or ROTC Pershing Rifles publications.
    - University of Idaho Drill Team, circa 1963; P002:280; 5X7 photographic print (Box 2)
      11th Regiment of Pershing Rifles, University of Idaho Drill team in formation at unidentified location. Other photographs in this series are from drill team competitions that OSC attended. This photo is probably related to P002:279 and a competition sponsored by the University of Idaho. Date unknown, circa 1962
    - Cadet (2) officers with Drill Competition Trophies 1962, March 1962; P002:328; 3.5x3.5 photographic print (Box 2)
      OSC Cadet officers displaying trophies from the Drill Team Competition 1961-62 which the unit won first place. Photo is marked on reverse: Major Lee Adams and Capt. Gary Butler, 11th Reg. Hq."
    - Cadet (3) Officers with Drill Competition Trophies 1962, March 1962; P002:329; 3.5x3.5 photographic print (Box 2)
      OSC Cadet officers displaying trophies from the Drill Team Competition 1961-62 which the unit won first place. Photo is marked on reverse:"Col. Jerome Jacoby, Lt. Col. Douglas hirfe (ex O.) Capt. Gary Butler (PIO) 11th Reg Hq"
    - OSU ROTC Drill team march in dress uniforms and tennis shoes, circa 1960; P002:438; 8X10 photographic print (Box 2)
      Caption on reverse: "Company E-11's crack drill team performs during the halftime intermission at a basketball game in Portland. Commanding Officer is 2nd Lt. Bill Myers." There is also a request to: "Please return this picture to: Commanding Officer, Company E-11, Oregon State University, Corvallis, Oregon" The drill team is in full dress uniforms with white tennis shoes (to protect Gym floor).
    - Company E-11 OSU Varsity Drill Team, Feb 1963, February 1963; P002:571; 3.5x3.5 photographic print (Box 2)
      Caption on reverse: "Co. E-11 Oregon State U. Varsity Drill Team on exhibition(sic). Also marked as 62-63 RGT 395. Photo of Drill Team formation on gym floor, full dress uniforms and white tennis shoes.
    - Company E-11 OSU ROTC Standing Inspection March 1963, P002:572; 3.5x5 photographic print (Box 2)
      Company E-11 OSU Pershing Rifles standing inspection by cadet officers. Photo is marked on reverse: "Co. E-11 Oregon State Univ, Freshman Drill team standing inspection"
    - OSU ROTC Freshman Drill Team inspection, Nov 1963, November 1963; P002:574; 3.5x5 photographic print (Box 2)
      Cadet officers inspection of OSU Freshman Drill Team on campus, November 1963. Photo is related to P002:572 from a different angle.
    - Hangar at Sand Point NAS with competition location., circa 1962; P002:443; 4X5 photographic print (Box 2)
      Drill competition location at Sand Point Naval Air Station in 1962. Interior shot of the hangar showing where the grand stand would be located.
    - Hangar at Sand Point Naval Air Station exterior view, circa 1962; P002:444; 4X5 photographic print (Box 2)
      Drill competition location at Sand Point Naval Air Station in 1962. Exterior view of the Hangar building.
    - Hangar at Sand Point Naval Air Station interior view #2, April 1962; P002:713; 3X4.5 photographic print (Box 2)
      ROTC Pershing Rifles Drill competition location at Sand Point Naval Air Station in 1962. Interior shot of the hangar. Military trailers in photo.
    - Cadet officers in Sand Point NAS Hangar, April 1962; P002:714; 3X4.5 photographic print (Box 2)
      ROTC Pershing Rifles Drill competition location at Sand Point Naval Air Station in 1962. Interior shot of the hangar. 4 cadet officers of OSU ROTC Pershing Rifles Drill team in photo, three are identified on reverse. Left to Right, Rod Stubbs, John Wilson, Jack Miller, CO for B-11 (unidentified cadet officer of another college unit) Noted as "this was taken Wed 11 April in the Hangar"
    - Sand Point NAS Drill competition 1962 negative #1, April 1962; P002:717; 2x2.5 negative (Box 2)
      Drill team with rifles in formation.
    - Sand Point NAS Drill competition 1962 negative #2, April 1962; P002:718; 2x2.5 negative (Box 2)
      Line of cadets at attention.
    - Sand Point NAS Drill competition 1962 negative #3, April 1962; P002:719; 2x2.5 negative (Box 2)
      Cadets in formation, passing rifles down the line.
    - Sand Point NAS Drill competition 1962 negative #4, April 1962; P002:720; 2x2.5 negative (Box 2)
      Drill team marching in circle formation.
    - Sand Point NAS Drill competition 1962 negative #5, April 1962; P002:721; 2x2.5 negative (Box 2)
      Close order drill formation.
    - Sand Point NAS Drill competition 1962 negative #6, April 1962; P002:722; 2x2.5 negative (Box 2)
      Drill team passing rifles, chrome helmets.
    - Sand Point NAS Drill competition 1962 negative #7, April 1962; P002:723; 2x2.5 negative (Box 2)
    - Sand Point NAS Drill competition 1962 negative #8, April 1962; P002:724; 2x2.5 negative (Box 2)
      Marching team with rifles.
    - Sand Point NAS Drill competition 1962 negative #9, April 1962; P002:725; 2x2.5 negative (Box 2)
      Cadet saluting officer in review. Female officer in photo.
    - Sand Point NAS Drill competition 1962 negative #10, April 1962; P002:726; 2x2.5 negative (Box 2)
      Column of cadets marching in formation, close order drill.
    - Sand Point NAS Drill competition 1962 negative #11, April 1962; P002:727; 2x2.5 negative (Box 2)
      Leader of drill team receiving trophy from female officer, formation in background.
    - Sand Point NAS Drill competition 1962 negative #12, April 1962; P002:728; 2x2.5 negative (Box 2)
      Trophy presentation to drill team leader dressed in fatigue uniform. Female officer presenting.
    - Sand Point NAS Drill competition 1962 negative #13, April 1962; P002:729; 2x2.5 negative (Box 2)
      Inspection of drill team by officer, checking rifles.
    - Sand Point NAS Drill competition 1962 negative #14, April 1962; P002:730; 2x2.5 negative (Box 2)
      Formation of cadets at attention with rifles at right shoulder arms. Awaiting inspection by officers.
    - Sand Point NAS Drill competition 1962 negative #15, April 1962; P002:731; 2x2.5 negative (Box 2)
      Inspection by US Army officer of cadet's M-1 Garand rifle.
    - Sand Point NAS Drill competition 1962 negative #16, April 1962; P002:732; 2x2.5 negative (Box 2)
      Formation of drill team cadets waiting for inspection.
    - Sand Point NAS Drill competition 1962 negative #17, April 1962; P002:733; 2x2.5 negative (Box 2)
      Another view of officer inspecting cadet's M-1 Garand rifle.
    - Sand Point NAS Drill competition 1962 negative #18, April 1962; P002:734; 2x2.5 negative (Box 2)
      Formation of cadets at attention with rifles at side, waiting for inspection.
    - Sand Point NAS Drill competition 1962 negative #19, April 1962; P002:735; 2x2.5 negative (Box 2)
      Rifle inspection by cadet officer with clip board.
    - Sand Point NAS Drill competition 1962 negative #20, April 1962; P002:736; 2x2.5 negative (Box 2)
      Cadet formation saluting officer.
    - Sand Point NAS Drill competition 1962 negative #21, April 1962; P002:737; 2x2.5 negative (Box 2)
      Group of officers reviewing cadets.
    - Sand Point NAS Drill competition 1962 negative #22, April 1962; P002:738; 2x2.5 negative (Box 2)
      Formation of cadets at attention with rifles raised.
    - Sand Point NAS Drill competition 1962 negative #23, April 1962; P002:739; 2x2.5 negative (Box 2)
      Cadets marching in formation with rifles.
    - Sand Point NAS Drill competition 1962 negative #24, April 1962; P002:740; 2x2.5 negative (Box 2)
    - Color 35mm Slides of Pershing Rifles Drill Team competition 1963
      Series of 20 color slides of the OSU Army ROTC Pershing Rifles Drill Team in various formations during their performance. Photos include marching drills, with rifle "tricks", and inspections of weapons and uniforms by officers. Uniforms depicted are dress coats with chrome helmets, khakis with berets and white laced boots. It is not certain if all drill units are from Oregon State, but the different uniforms and groups are probably separate platoons or companies within the Pershing Rifles Regiment in attendance. Also included are slides of the Military Ball including coed sponsors and their escorts. Many of the slides have been reproduced for publication in OSC and Pershing Rifles periodicals. The original packaging of this series was the mailing box from the processing laboratory. Addressed to Rod Commons, 301 Waldo Hall, Corvallis Oregon. Photocopy of box label maintained in file, slides transferred to protective sleeves.
      - Color Slide Military Ball Ft. Lewis 1963, April 1963; P002:335; 35mm Color Slide (Box 2)
        Color 35mm Slide. OSU Army ROTC Pershing Rifles Drill Team in various formations during their performance.
      - Color Slide Military Ball, Ft. Lewis 1963, April 1963; P002:337; 35mm Color Slide (Box 2)
        Military ball, Ft. Lewis WA, April 1963
      - Color Slide, Coed Sponsors, 11th Regiment Pershing Rifles, April 1963; P002:338; 35mm Color Slide (Box 2)
        Military Ball including coed sponsors and their escorts.
      - Color Slide, Military Ball, Ft. Lewis 1963, April 1963; P002:339; 35mm Color Slide (Box 2)
        Slide of the Military Ball including coed sponsors and their escorts.
      - Color slide, Coed sponsors, military ball, Ft. Lewis 1963, April 1963; P002:340; 35mm Color Slide (Box 2)
      - Color slide, Military ball, Ft. Lewis Trophy presentation, April 1963; P002:341; 35mm Color Slide (Box 2)
        Trophy presentation with coed sponsors, Ft. Lewis 1963
      - Color Slide, trophy presentation, Military Ball, Ft. Lewis 1963, April 1963; P002:342; 35mm Color Slide (Box 2)
        Military Ball, Ft. Lewis trophy presentation
      - Color Slide, Trophy presentation Military Ball, Ft. Lewis 1963, April 1963; P002:343; 35mm Color Slide (Box 2)
        Trophy presentation, Ft. Lewis 1963
      - Color Slide, Ft. Lewis Drill Team Competition 1963, April 1963; P002:344; 35mm Color Slide (Box 2)
        OSU Army ROTC Pershing Rifles Drill Team in various formations during their performance.
      - Color Slide, Ft. Lewis Drill Team Competition,trophy display, April 1963; P002:345; 35mm Color Slide (Box 2)
        Trophy display table, Ft. Lewis Drill Competition, April 1963.
      - Color Slide, Coed Sponsors, Military Ball Ft. Lewis 1963, April 1963; P002:346; 35mm Color Slide (Box 2)
        Military Ball, Ft. Lewis Coed Sponsors
      - Color Slide, Coed Sponsors, Ft. Lewis Competition, 1963, April 1963; P002:347; 35mm Color Slide (Box 2)
        Military Ball, Ft. Lewis Coed Sponsors.
      - Color Slide, Drill Team Competition, Ft. Lewis, 1963, April 1963; P002:348; 35mm Color Slide (Box 2)
        Drill team on floor at Ft. Lewis 1963
      - Color Slide, Drill Team Competition, Ft. Lewis 1963, April 1963; P002:349; 35mm Color Slide (Box 2)
        Rifle inspection at competition, Ft. Lewis 1963
      - Color Slide, Drill Team on Floor, Ft. Lewis 1963, April 1963; P002:350; 35mm Color Slide (Box 2)
        Drill team on Floor, Ft. Lewis 1963
      - Color Slide, Trophy presentation, Ft. Lewis 1963, April 1963; P002:351; 35mm Color Slide (Box 2)
        Trophy presentation, Ft. Lewis competition, 1963.
      - Color Slide Drill Team Competition, Ft. Lewis 1963, April 1963; P002:352; 35mm Color Slide (Box 2)
      - Color Slide, Drill Team on floor, Ft. Lewis 1963, April 1963; P002:353; 35mm Color Slide (Box 2)
        Drill team in performance
      - Color Slide, Trophy Presentation Ft. Lewis Competition 1963, April 1963; P002:354; 35mm Color Slide (Box 2)
      - Color Slide, Drill team competition, Ft. Lewis, 1963, April 1963; P002:355; 35mm Color Slide (Box 2)
        Drill team competition, Ft. Lewis 1963.
      - Army ROTC Pershing Rifles Drill Team Competition, April 1963; P002:227 - P002:244 (Box 2)
        Group of 15 color and b/w prints of the OSU ROTC Pershing Rifles Drill Team in various formations during their performance. Photos include marching drills, with rifle "tricks", and inspections of weapons and uniforms by officers. Uniforms depicted are dress coats with chrome helmets, khakis with berets and white laced boots. Some photos show full dress uniforms and white tennis shoes (to protect gym floor?). One of the images is available online.
  - ROTC Pershing Rifles Coed Sponsors/Military Balls/Award Ceremonies, circa 1960
    sub series contains stock photographs of Coed Sponsors (Escorts to Military Banquets and Balls). Competition for Queens used these photographs for promotional materials. Some photographs of Cadets in dress uniforms with Coed Sponsors may have been used in OSU publications. Many of the photographs are stock 8x10 portraits, taken by US Army Photographers. Names of coeds are listed where available.
    - Pershing Rifles Sponsors - coeds 1962, January 1962; P002:330; 8X10 photographic print (Box 2)
      Photo shows 3 coeds in a posed portrait. Caption reads: L to R Miss Susan Schumacher, Miss Phillis Mullan, Miss Julie Holm, Pershing Rifles Sponsors" Dated 22 Jan 1962, photo by Mr. Loyal Lauritzen, Signal Photo Lab, US Army Garrison, Fort Lawton, Washington.
    - Coed Sponsor Corps 11th Regiment, Lucille Kroll, circa 1961; P002:273; 3X5 photographic print (Box 2)
      Studio photograph of Brenda Lucille Droll, Company B - 11th Regiment. She has honors received listed as "Honorary company commander, Company B, 11th Regt. and Cadet Captain of Coed Sponsor Corps (Newly organized). She is listed as age 19years, Sophomore, Major Education and hometown of Seattle Washington. The photo is from Walters Studio, Seattle Washington.
    - Candidate for Queen - Pershing Rifles Ball, February 1961; P002:272; 1.0 3 x 5 prints; 8X10 photographic print (Box 2)
      Portrait of Valerie Haener, candidate for Queen, ROTC Pershing Rifles Military Ball, Seattle University. Photographer Kay Alderson, Signal Photo Lab, US Army Garrison, Fort Lawton, Washington.
    - Pershing Rifles Queen, January 1964; P002:275; 8X10 photographic print (Box 2)
      US Army photograph of Pershing Rifles Queen, Sara Griffith, Company B-11, University of Washington. Photographer Mr. Loyal Lauritzen, Signal Photo Division, US Army Garrison, Fort Lawton, Washington. This photograph may be related to the OSC visit to the 1961 Pershing Rifles Drill Team Competition and was included in a press packet sent to Oregon State. Date of photograph 21 Jan 1964 places this event in the 1963-64 ROTC year.
    - 11th Regiment Sponsor, C-11 University of Idaho, circa 1961; P002:274; 5X7 photographic print (Box 2)
      11th Regiment Sponsor, Miss Delores Llewellyn, C-11, University of Idaho. This photograph may be related to the OSC visit to the 1961 Pershing Rifles Drill Team Competition and was included in a press packet sent to Oregon State. Date of photograph 2 Feb 61 places this event in the 1961-62 ROTC year, which Oregon State won first place at competition of drill teams.
    - 11th Regiment Sponsor G-11 1957-58, circa 1957; P002:276; 8X10 photographic print (Box 2)
      Stock studio portrait of 11th Regiment, Pershing Rifles coed sponsor from 1957-58 year, Kaye Tomlinson.
    - Pershing Rifles Queen 10 semi-finalists 1963, November 1963; P002:277; 8X10 photographic print (Box 2)
      Dated November 1963, US Army photo of "The ten semi-finalists for Pershing and Rifles Queen, are from left to right, Miss Linda Nielson, Miss Linda Nethercup, Miss Brenda Lee, Miss Judy Crossett, Miss Judy Burke, Miss Cindy Thal, Miss Sara Griffith, Miss Joy Prosser, Miss Betsy Roberts and Miss Jo Ann Horn; Army ROTC, University of Washington, Seattle, Washington." In pencil, "The princesses are Miss Linda Nethercup, Miss Cindy Thal, Miss Joy Prosser and Miss Jo Ann Horn." Photograph taken by SP/5 Leroy Sundberg, Signal Photo Division, US Army Garrison, Fort Lawton, Washington. Date of photograph Nov 1963 places this event in the 1962-63 ROTC year, which Oregon State College Drill Team attended competition at Ft. Lewis.
    - Entry to Sponsor Contest Pershing Rifles 1956, circa 1956; P002:278; 8X10 photographic print (Box 2)
      Listed as entry to Sponsor Contest 1956. Identification in lower left corner in pencil "Evelyn Ribary, sponsored by Company D, 11th Regiment, State College of Washington." Photo is stamped Midway Photo Shop, 802 Colorado, Pullman Washington.
    - 11th Regiment Sponsor - undated U of WA, circa 1960; P002:279; 8X10 photographic print (Box 2)
      Studio portrait of 11th Regiment Coed Sponsor from early 1960s. Identified as Janette Rees, Sponsor Co. B-11, University of Washington. Photograph is in same series of head shots of coed sponsors, probably for candidate for Queen of Military Ball.
    - Navy ROTC Cadet and escort, Navy Ring Dance, circa 1960; P002:566; 4X5 photographic print (Box 2)
      Print 4x5. Navy ROTC Cadet officer, Erskine Austin and his escort Melinda Rickson at the Navy Ring Dance, circa1960. Two copies of photo, one marked on reverse with "Barometer Photo" stamp, dated 4/6 (no year).
    - Cadet officers at Military ball, circa 1960; P002:744; 3.5X5 photographic print (Box 2)
      Posed photograph of ROTC officer cadets at military ball, circa 1960. All services represented, with coed sponsor at center. Uniforms of the post WWII style, with bow ties and shoulder braids. Naval officers in dress whites.
    - Portrait of Pershing Rifles coed sponsor, unidentified, circa 1960; P002:796; 5X7 photographic print (Box 2)
      Stock studio portrait. Unidentified coed sponsor of the 11th Regiment, Pershing Rifles. The portrait is similar to others in collection of the young women acting as escorts to the Pershing Rifles military balls held on campus. Photos were used in competition for Queen.
    - Portrait of Pershing Rifles coed sponsor unidentified #2, circa 1960; P002:797; 4X3 photographic print (Box 2)
      Unidentified coed sponsor of the 11th Regiment, Pershing Rifles. The portrait is similar to others in collection of the young women acting as escorts to the Pershing Rifles military balls held on campus. Photos were used in competition for Queen. Notation on reverse: "This photo for article in "Pershing Rifleman" from Company C-11."
    - Portrait of Pershing Rifles coed sponsor unidentified #3, circa 1960; P002:798; 3.5X5 photographic print (Box 2)
      Unidentified coed sponsor of the 11th Regiment, Pershing Rifles. The portrait is similar to others in collection of the young women acting as escorts to the Pershing Rifles military balls held on campus. Photos were used in competition for Queen.
    - Portrait of Pershing Rifles coed sponsor unidentified #4, circa 1960; P002:799; 5X4 photographic print (Box 2)